offersandclicks.info 2013-06-09

# Offers And Clicks : Privacy Policy

**Privacy Notice**

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (website address). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.  
2\. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.  
3\. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.  
4\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about changes to this privacy policy or Term or service and other server/web site information. If you don\'t want to receive these emails you can be a member on the site and must delete your account. We have paid emails in which you can opt-out through your user account.

Your Access to and Control Over Information  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

* See what data we have about you, if any.  
* Change/correct any data we have about you.  
* Have us delete any data we have about you.  
* Express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

Security  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. Most payment for products/services on the site are paid through a payment processor. So you must verify the link for the payment processor site is correct and notify us if there is a breach.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us.
